productivity growth will accelerate
to the 4% to
6% range and be
sustained there. Normally, we
see a cyclical peak
around there and then
it falls back. We
think it will be
sustained, and we think
that by the end
of this decade, real
GDP growth could be
averaging more than 7%
per year. Wow. And
I know that sounds
shocking- Yeah given that
we've been at 3%
for 125 years.
But it is the
history associated with technology
revolutions, a step change
upIn GDP growth The
productivity increase, the GDP
growth that you are
forecasting as a result
of these disruptive technologies,
to what extent is
that the result of
fewer people doing more?
My question is about
job losses as a
result of this technology,
because if everything that
investors are betting on
when it comes to
this AI revolution comes
true, it means that
companies aren't going to
need as many people
to do a lot
more. What does that
look like?